Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part One
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Files, 1710-1955; 21.07; (65 boxes)
  - Derby, Edward George Geoffrey Smith Stanley, Earl of, 1799-1869, 1854-74, undated (Box 21, Folder 724)
  - Derby, Edward Henry Stanley, Earl of, 1826-1893, 1866 (Box 21, Folder 725)
  - Derby, Frederick Arthur Stanley, Earl of, 1841-1908, 1879 (Box 21, Folder 726)
  - De Ros, William Lennox Lascelles Fitzgerald, Baron, 1797-1874, 1889, undated (Box 21, Folder 727)
  - Des Voeux, Charles, Sir, Bart., 1779- 1858, 1838 (Box 21, Folder 728)
  - Desart, Elizabeth Lucy (Campbell) Cuffe, Countess of, 1822-1898, 1842, undated (Box 21, Folder 729)
  - De Saumarez, James Saumarez, Baron, 1789-1863, 1837 (Box 21, Folder 730)
  - De Tabley, George Fleming Warren, Baron, 1811-1877, undated (Box 21, Folder 731)
  - Devon, William Courtenay, Earl of, 1777-1859, 1838, undated (Box 21, Folder 732)
  - Devon, William Reginald Courtenay, Earl of, 1807-1888, 1839-85 (Box 21, Folder 733)
  - Devonshire, Spencer Compton Cavendish, Duke of, 1833-1908, 1851-76, undated (Box 21, Folder 734)
  - Devonshire, William Cavendish, Duke of, 1808-1891, 1831-85, undated (Box 21, Folder 735)
  - Devonshire, William Spencer Cavendish, Duke of, 1790-1858, 1833-55, undated (Box 21, Folder 736)
  - Dhuleep Singh, Maharajah of Lahore, 1838-1893, 1866, undated (Box 21, Folder 737)
  - Dicey, Albert Venn, 1835-1922, 1895-1901 (Box 21, Folder 738)
  - Dick, Cotsford, 1846-1911, undated (Box 21, Folder 739)
  - Dick, James Nicholas, Sir, b. 1832, 1890 (Box 21, Folder 740)
  - Dickens, Charles, 1812-1870, undated (Box 21, Folder 741)
  - Dickens, Charles, 1837-1896, 1887, undated (Box 21, Folder 742)
  - Dickinson, G. Lowes (Goldsworthy Lowes), 1862-1932, undated (Box 21, Folder 743)
  - Dicksee, Francis Bernard, Sir, 1853- 1928, undated (Box 21, Folder 744)
  - Diehl, Alice M. (Alice Mangold), 1844- 1912, 1902 (Box 21, Folder 745)
  - Dilke, Ashton Wentworth, 1850-1883, 1882 (Box 21, Folder 746)
  - Dilke, Charles Wentworth, 1789-1864, 1829 (Box 21, Folder 747)
  - Dilke, Charles Wentworth, Sir, 1810- 1869, 1837 (Box 21, Folder 748)
  - Dilke, Charles Wentworth, Sir, 1843- 1911, 1868-1904, undated (Box 21, Folder 749)
  - Dilke, Katherine Mary Eliza (Sheil), d. 1874, undated (Box 21, Folder 750)
  - Dillenius, John James, 1687-1747, 1732-33 (Box 21, Folder 751)
  - Dillon, Martin Andrew, Sir, 1826-1913, 1904 (Box 21, Folder 752)
  - Disraeli, Coningsby Ralph, 1867-1936, 1893-1935, undated (Box 21, Folder 753)
  - Disraeli, Ralph, 1809-1898, 1866 (Box 21, Folder 754)
  - Distant, William Lucas, 1845-1922, 1890 (Box 21, Folder 755)
  - Dixie, Florence Douglas, Lady, 1857- 1905, 1883-1903, undated (Box 21, Folder 756)
  - Dixon, John, 1878, undated (Box 21, Folder 757)
  - Dobell, Sydney, 1824-1874, undated (Box 21, Folder 758)
  - D'Orsay, Lawrence, b. 1850, 1897 (Box 21, Folder 759)
  - Dorset, Charles Sackville-Germain, Duke of, 1767-1843, undated (Box 21, Folder 760)
  - Doubleday, H. Arthur (Herbert Arthur), 1867-1941, 1900-1902 (Box 21, Folder 761)
  - Douglas, W. Fetter, 1882 (Box 21, Folder 762)
  - Dowker, George, 1889 (Box 21, Folder 763)
  - Doyle, Francis Hastings, Sir, 1810- 1888, 1885-88, undated (Box 21, Folder 764)
  - Drake, Charles F. Tyrwhitt (Charles Frederick Tyrwhitt), 1846-1874, 1873 (Box 22, Folder 765)
  - Drew, Mary Gladstone, 1847-1927, 1898 (Box 22, Folder 766)
  - Drummond, Flora, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 767)
  - Ducie, Henry John Reynolds-Moreton, Earl of, 1827-1921, 1872-1908, undated (Box 22, Folder 768)
  - Ducie, Julia (Langston) Reynolds- Moreton, Countess of, d. 1895, undated (Box 22, Folder 769)
  - Duckworth, Robinson, 1834-1911, 1869-1908, undated (Box 22, Folder 770)
  - Duclaux, Agnes Mary Frances Robinson, 1857-1944
    See: Robinson, A. Mary F. (Agnes Mary Frances), 1857-1944, box 50, folder 1826
  - Dufferin and Ava, Frederick Temple Blackwood, Marquis of, 1826-1902, 1892-97 (Box 22, Folder 771)
  - Dufferin and Ava, Harriot Georgina Blackwood, Marchioness of, 1843-1936, 1884-1902 (Box 22, Folder 772)
  - Dugourd and Co., Paris, 1897 (Box 22, Folder 773)
  - Duke, James, Sir, Bart., 1792-1873, 1861 (Box 22, Folder 774)
  - Du Maurier, George, 1834-1896, undated (Box 22, Folder 775)
  - Dundas, J. D., 1835 (Box 22, Folder 776)
  - Dunster, William Hilliard, 1842 (Box 22, Folder 777)
  - Du Plat, Charles Taylor, Sir, b. 1822, undated (Box 22, Folder 778)
  - Durham, George Frederick D'Arcy Lambton, Earl of, 1828-1879, 1850-70, undated (Box 22, Folder 779)
  - Durham, John George Lambton, Earl of, 1792-1840, 1834 (Box 22, Folder 780)
  - Durham, Joseph, 1814-1877, 1874 (Box 22, Folder 781)
  - Durnford, Richard, 1802-1895, 1880-93, undated (Box 22, Folder 782)
  - Durrant, J. R., 1846 (Box 22, Folder 783)
  - Dwarris, Fortunatus, Sir, 1786-1860, undated (Box 22, Folder 784)
  - Dyke, William Hart, 1837-1931, undated (Box 22, Folder 785)
  - Dyson, Frank Watson, 1868-1939, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 786)
  - Eardley, Culling Eardley, Sir, 1805- 1863, 1842, undated (Box 22, Folder 787)
  - Earle, Alfred, Bp. of Marlborough, 1827-1918, 1897, undated (Box 22, Folder 788)
  - Earle, William, 1833-1885, 1884 (Box 22, Folder 789)
  - East, Alfred, Sir, 1849-1913, 1908, undated (Box 22, Folder 790)
  - Eastlake, Charles Lock, Sir, 1793-1865, undated (Box 22, Folder 791)
  - Eastlake, Elizabeth Rigby, Lady, 1809- 1893, 1834, undated (Box 22, Folder 792)
  - Eastlake, Mary, 1889, undated (Box 22, Folder 793)
  - Eden, George Rodney, Bp. of Wakefield, 1853-1940, 1893-94 (Box 22, Folder 794)
  - Edersheim, Alfred, 1825-1889, 1888 (Box 22, Folder 795)
  - Edgcumbe, Richard, 1843-1937, 1912 (Box 22, Folder 796)
  - Edwardes, Edward Tickner, 1865-1944, 1929-45 (Box 22, Folder 797)
  - Edwardes, George, 1832-1915, 1894-96, undated (Box 22, Folder 798)
  - Edwardes, Herbert B. (Herbert Benjamin), Sir, 1819-1868, 1863-66, undated (Box 22, Folder 799)
  - Edward VII, King of Great Britain, 1841-1910, 1845-1910 (Box 22, Folder 800)
  - Edward, Prince of Saxe-Weimar, 1823- 1902, 1864-99 (Box 22, Folder 801)
  - Edward Augustus, Duke of Kent, 1767- 1820, 1802-1819, undated (Box 22, Folder 802)
  - Edwards, Amelia Ann Blanford, 1831- 1892, 1865, undated (Box 22, Folder 803)
  - Edwards, Catherine Adelaide, 1887 (Box 22, Folder 804)
  - Edwards, H. Sutherland (Henry Sutherland), 1828-1906, 1887 (Box 22, Folder 805)
  - Edwards, Fleetwood Isham, Sir, 1842- 1910, 1896 (Box 22, Folder 806)
  - Edwards, J. C., 1882 (Box 22, Folder 807)
  - Effingham, Henry Howard, Earl of, 1806-1889, 1847, undated (Box 23, Folder 808)
  - Effingham, Kenneth Alexander Howard, Earl of, 1767-1845, 1822, undated (Box 23, Folder 809)
  - Egan, Tom, 1867 (Box 23, Folder 810)
  - Egerton, Mr., 1847 (Box 23, Folder 811)
  - Eglington, Archibald William Montgomerie, Earl of, 1812-1861, 1839-52, undated (Box 23, Folder 812)
  - Eldée, Lilian, 1903, undated (Box 23, Folder 813)
  - Eldon, John Scott, Earl of, 1805-1854, 1844 (Box 23, Folder 814)
  - Elgin, Victor Alexander Bruce, Earl of, 1849-1917, 1887 (Box 23, Folder 815)
  - Eliot, Philip Frank, 1835-1917, 1891-94 (Box 23, Folder 816)
  - Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, b. 1926, 1950-55 (Box 23, Folder 817)
  - Ellenborough, Edward Law, Earl of, 1790-1871, 1845-66, undated (Box 23, Folder 818)
  - Ellicott, C. J. (Charles John), 1819- 1905, 1874-86, undated (Box 23, Folder 819)
  - Elliott, E. B. (Edward Bishop), 1793- 1875, 1861 (Box 23, Folder 820)
  - Ellis, Arthur Edward Augustus, Sir, 1837-1907, 1903, undated (Box 23, Folder 821)
  - Ellis, Robinson, 1834-1913, 1898, undated (Box 23, Folder 822)
  - Ellis, William, 1794-1872, 1866, undated (Box 23, Folder 823)
  - Elmsley, Peter, 1773-1825, 1825, undated (Box 23, Folder 824)
  - Elphinstone, Howard Crawford, Sir, 1829-1890, 1888 (Box 23, Folder 825)
  - Elphinstone, John Elphinstone, Baron, 1807-1860, 1835, undated (Box 23, Folder 826)
  - Else Family, 1837 (Box 23, Folder 827)
  - Elvey, George J., 1816-1893, 1850 (Box 23, Folder 828)
  - Elwes, Henry John, 1846-1922, 1885-89, undated (Box 23, Folder 829)
  - Elwin, Whitwell, 1816-1900, 1859 (Box 23, Folder 830)
  - Ely, Jane (Hope-Vere) Loftus, Marchioness of, 1821-1890, undated (Box 23, Folder 831)
  - Emery, Isabel Winifred, 1862-1924, 1886-1918, undated (Box 23, Folder 832-833)
  - Emery, William, 1825-1910, 1878-1907, undated (Box 23, Folder 834)
  - Enfield Chemical Manure and Irrigation Company, 1874 (Box 23, Folder 835)
  - English, Isaac, 1836 (Box 23, Folder 836)
  - Enright, Richard W., 1880 (Box 23, Folder 837)
  - Eon de Beaumont, Charles Geneviève Louis Auguste André Timothée d', 1728-1810, undated (Box 23, Folder 838)
  - Erle, T. W. (Twynihoe William), 1828-1908, 1870 (Box 23, Folder 839)
  - Erle, William, Sir, 1793-1880, 1860-68 (Box 23, Folder 840)
  - Ernest Augustus, King of Hanover, 1777-1851, 1819-1838 (Box 23, Folder 841)
  - Ernst I, Duke of Saxe-Coburg-Gotha, 1784-1844, 1832 (Box 23, Folder 842)
  - Erroll, Eliza Amelia (Gore), Countess of, 1829-1916, 1886-96 (Box 23, Folder 843)
  - Erroll, William George Hay, Earl of, 1801-1846, 1837-43 (Box 23, Folder 844)
  - Erskine, Henry David, Sir, 1838-1921, 1897, undated (Box 23, Folder 845)
  - Escott, T.H.S. (Thomas Hay Sweet), 1844-1924, 1904-06, undated (Box 23, Folder 846)
  - Esher, William Baliol Brett, Viscount, 1815-1899, 1895, undated (Box 23, Folder 847)
  - Esmond, H. V. (Henry V.), 1869- 1922, undated (Box 23, Folder 848)
  - Essex, Catherine (Stephens) Capel- Coningsby, Countess of, 1794-1882, undated (Box 23, Folder 849)
  - Estcourt, Thomas Henry Sutton Sotheron, 1801-1876, 1858 (Box 23, Folder 850)
  - Ettrick, Francis Napier, Baron, 1819- 1898, 1857 (Box 23, Folder 851)
  - Evans, George de Lacy, Sir, 1787-1870, 1850-67 (Box 23, Folder 852)
  - Evans, J. Nathan, 1882 (Box 23, Folder 853)
  - Evelyn, William John, 1822-1908, undated (Box 23, Folder 854)
  - Everett, George, 1874 (Box 23, Folder 855)
  - Everett-Green, Evelyn, 1856-1932, 1902-04, undated (Box 23, Folder 856)
  - Eversley, Charles Shaw-Lefevre, Viscount, 1794-1888, 1836-73 (Box 23, Folder 857)
  - Ewald, Ferdinand Christian, 1802-1874, undated (Box 23, Folder 858)
  - Exeter, Brownlow Cecil, Marquess of, 1795-1867, 1860-65 (Box 23, Folder 859)
  - Exeter, Plymouth, and Devonport Railway, 1846 (Box 23, Folder 860)
  - Exeter, William Alleyne Cecil, Marquess of, 1825-1895, 1870-92, undated (Box 23, Folder 861)
  - Exmouth, Edward Pellew, Viscount, 1811-1876, undated (Box 23, Folder 862)
  - Exmouth, Lady Georgiana Janet (Dick) Pellew, Viscountess, 1800?-1870, undated (Box 23, Folder 863)
  - Eyton, Charles E., 1863 (Box 23, Folder 864)
  - Ezekiel, Moses Jacob, b. 1844, undated (Box 23, Folder 865)
  - Faed, John, 1819-1902, undated (Box 24, Folder 866)
  - Faed, Thomas, 1826-1900, undated (Box 24, Folder 867)
  - Fairbairn, T., 1883 (Box 24, Folder 868)
  - Fairbairn, William, Sir, 1789-1874, 1848 (Box 24, Folder 869)
  - Faija, Guglielmo, undated (Box 24, Folder 870)
  - Falconer, Edmund, 1814-1879, 1873 (Box 24, Folder 871)
  - Falmouth, George Henry Boscawen, Earl of, 1811-1852, 1844-52 (Box 24, Folder 872)
  - Faning, Joseph Eaton, 1850-1927, 1907 (Box 24, Folder 873)
  - Fanshawe, Edward Gennys, Sir, 1814- 1906, undated (Box 24, Folder 874)
  - Farkoa, Maurice, b. 1864, 1897-1901, undated (Box 24, Folder 875)
  - Farley, Charles, 1771-1859, undated (Box 24, Folder 876)
  - Farquhar, Gilbert, b. 1850, 1897, undated (Box 24, Folder 877)
  - Farquhar, J. N. (John Nicol), 1861-1929, 1884-90 (Box 24, Folder 878)
  - Farrar, Frederic William, 1831-1903, 1891, undated (Box 24, Folder 879)
  - Farrar, L. M., undated (Box 24, Folder 880)
  - Farren, Ellen, 1848-1904, undated (Box 24, Folder 881)
  - Farren, Josephine, 1864 (Box 24, Folder 882)
  - Farren, William, 1786-1861, undated (Box 24, Folder 883)
  - Farren, William, 1825-1908, 1894 (Box 24, Folder 884)
  - Faucit, Helen Saville, 1817-1898, 1897, undated (Box 24, Folder 885)
  - Fearon, Robert Bryce, 1839 (Box 24, Folder 886)
  - Featherstone, Vane, 1894, undated (Box 24, Folder 887)
  - Fechter, Charles, 1824-1879, undated (Box 24, Folder 888)
  - Fellows, Charles, Sir, 1799-1860, undated (Box 24, Folder 889)
  - Fenn, Frederick, 1868-1924, 1894 (Box 24, Folder 890)
  - Fenn, George Manville, 1831-1909, 1894, undated (Box 24, Folder 891)
  - Fenton, Edward Dyne, d. 1880, 1858 (Box 24, Folder 892)
  - Ferguson, Robert, 1799-1865, 1858 (Box 24, Folder 893)
  - Fergusson, James, Sir, 1787-1865, undated (Box 24, Folder 894)
  - Fergusson, William, Sir, 1808-1877, 1850 (Box 24, Folder 895)
  - Fernandez, Henry, 1875 (Box 24, Folder 896)
  - Fernandez, James, 1835-1915, 1893-1903, undated (Box 24, Folder 897)
  - Festing, John Wogan, Bp. of St. Albans, 1837-1902, undated (Box 24, Folder 898)
  - Feversham, Mabel Violet (Graham) Duncombe, Countess, d. 1915, 1868 (Box 24, Folder 899)
  - Feversham, William Duncombe, Baron, 1798-1867, 1853-64, undated (Box 24, Folder 900)
  - Field, Henry M., 1873 (Box 24, Folder 901)
  - Field, William Ventris Field, Baron, 1813-1907, 1872, undated (Box 24, Folder 902)
  - Fife, Alexander William George Duff, Duke of, 1849-1912, 1889-1900, undated (Box 24, Folder 903)
  - Fingall, Arthur James Plunkett, Earl of, 1791-1869, 1855 (Box 24, Folder 904)
  - Firminger, Walter K. (Walter Kelly), 1870-1940, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 905)
  - Fisher, David, 1788-1858, undated (Box 25, Folder 906)
  - Fisher, David, 1816-1887, 1854 (Box 25, Folder 907)
  - Fisher, Herbert, 1866-88 (Box 25, Folder 908)
  - Fisher, John, 1748-1825, 1822 (Box 25, Folder 909)
  - Fisher, William, 1780-1852, 1847 (Box 25, Folder 910)
  - Fitton, William Henry, 1780-1861, 1835 (Box 25, Folder 911)
  - Fitzclarence, Lord Adolphus, 1802-1856, 1849, undated (Box 25, Folder 912)
  - Fitzclarence, Lord Frederick, 1799- 1854, 1837-47 (Box 25, Folder 913)
  - Fitzgeorge, Augustus Charles Frederick, Sir, 1847-1933, 1885-99, undated (Box 25, Folder 914)
  - Fitzgeorge, George William Adolphus, 1843, 1881-90 (Box 25, Folder 915)
  - Fitzgerald, William George, b. 1872, 1897 (Box 25, Folder 916)
  - Fitzhardinge, Charlotte (Reynolds- Moreton) Berkeley, Baroness, 1806-1881, 1863 (Box 25, Folder 917)
  - Fitzhardinge, Maurice Frederick Fitzhardinge Berkeley, Baron, 1788- 1867, undated (Box 25, Folder 918)
  - Fitzhardinge, William Fitzhardinge Berkeley, Earl of, 1786-1857, undated (Box 25, Folder 919)
  - Fitzroy, Lady Anne (Cavendish), 1787- 1871, 1846 (Box 25, Folder 920)
  - Fitzroy, Lord Charles, 1791-1865, 1846 (Box 25, Folder 921)
  - Fitzroy, Lord Frederick John, 1823- 1919, 1875 (Box 25, Folder 922)
  - Fitzroy, Robert, 1805-1865, 1857-64 (Box 25, Folder 923)
  - Fitzroy, Lord William, 1782-1857, 1841 (Box 25, Folder 924)
  - Fitzwilliam, Charles William Wentworth, Earl, 1786-1857, 1824-57 (Box 25, Folder 925)
  - Fitzwilliam, William Charles de Meuron, Earl, 1872-1943, 1923 (Box 25, Folder 926)
  - Fitzwygram, F. (Frederick), Sir, 1823- 1904, undated (Box 25, Folder 927)
  - Fleming, George, 1858-1938
    See: Fletcher, Constance, 1858-1938, box 25, folder 928
  - Fleming, John, 1785-1857, undated (Box 25, Folder 928)
  - Fletcher, Constance, 1858-1938, undated (Box 25, Folder 929)
  - Florence, Annie, undated (Box 25, Folder 930)
  - Flower, Helen, undated (Box 25, Folder 931)
  - Flower, William Henry, 1831-1899, 1894 (Box 25, Folder 932)
  - Foley, John Henry, 1818-1874, 1863-72, undated (Box 25, Folder 933)
  - Foli, Allan James, 1837-1899, undated (Box 25, Folder 934)
  - Folkes, William John Henry Browne, Sir, Bart., 1786-1860, 1845 (Box 25, Folder 935)
  - Forbes, James David, 1809-1868, undated (Box 25, Folder 936)
  - Forbes-Robertson, Johnston, Sir, 1853- 1937, 1885-1917 (Box 25, Folder 937)
  - Forbes-Robertson, Norman, 1859-1932, 1891 (Box 25, Folder 938)
  - Ford, Edward Onslow, 1852-1901, 1888-91, undated (Box 25, Folder 939)
  - Forestier, Amédée, d. 1930, 1902, undated (Box 25, Folder 940)
  - Forman, Alma (Murray), 1897 (Box 25, Folder 941)
  - Forrester, Henry, 1880, undated (Box 25, Folder 942)
  - Forster, William, 1784-1854, 1843 (Box 26, Folder 943)
  - Forster, W. E. (William Edward), 1818- 1886, 1878-83, undated (Box 26, Folder 944)
  - Forster, William Frederick, Sir, 1873 (Box 26, Folder 945)
  - Forster-Cooper, Clive, Sir, 1880-1947, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 946)
  - Fortescue, Hugh Fortescue, Earl, 1818- 1905, 1840-61, undated (Box 26, Folder 947)
  - Fortescue, May, b. 1862, 1894, undated (Box 26, Folder 948)
  - Foss, Edward, 1787-1870, 1855-56 (Box 26, Folder 949)
  - Foster, John, 1868 (Box 26, Folder 950)
  - Foster, Murel, 1877-1937, undated (Box 26, Folder 951)
  - Foulis, William, 1838 (Box 26, Folder 952)
  - Fowler, Edith Henrietta, 1865-1944, 1887 (Box 26, Folder 953)
  - Fowler, Emily, undated (Box 26, Folder 954)
  - Fowler, Mary Lemon
    See: Waller, Mary Lemon (Fowler), box 61, folder 2218
  - Fowler, Montague, Sir, Bart., 1858- 1933, 1898 (Box 26, Folder 955)
  - Fowler, Thomas, 1832-1904, undated (Box 26, Folder 956)
  - Frampton, George James, Sir, 1860-1928, 1894-95 (Box 26, Folder 957)
  - Franks, Augustus Wollaston, Sir, 1826- 1897, 1865-87, undated (Box 26, Folder 958)
  - Fremantle, Arthur James Lyon, Sir, 1835-1901, 1880-90 (Box 26, Folder 959)
  - Fremantle, C. W., 1868, undated (Box 26, Folder 960)
  - Fremantle, William Robert, 1807-1895, 1887-93, undated (Box 26, Folder 961)
  - French, John Denton Pinkstone, Earl of Ypres, 1852-1925, 1906, undated (Box 26, Folder 962)
  - Freshfield, Douglas William, 1845-1934, 1889-93 (Box 26, Folder 963)
  - Frickenhaus, Fanny, undated (Box 26, Folder 964)
  - Fripp, Alfred Downing, Sir, 1865-1930, 1907 (Box 26, Folder 965)
  - Frost, John, 1750-1842, undated (Box 26, Folder 966)
  - Froude, James Anthony, 1818-1894, undated (Box 26, Folder 967)
  - Fry, Edward, Sir, 1827-1918, 1909 (Box 26, Folder 968)
  - Fryers, Austin, undated (Box 26, Folder 969)
  - Fulcher, G. W. (George Williams), 1795-1855, 1847 (Box 26, Folder 970)
  - Furniss, Harry, 1854-1925, 1854-1902, undated (Box 26, Folder 971)
  - Gainsborough, Charles George Noel, Earl, 1818-1881, 1818, undated (Box 26, Folder 972)
  - Gainsborough, Frances (Jocelyn) Noel, Countess of, 1814-1885, undated (Box 26, Folder 973)
  - Galton, Blanche, undated (Box 26, Folder 974)
  - Galton, Francis, Sir, 1822-1911, 1869 (Box 26, Folder 975)
  - Galway, George Edward Arundell Monckton-Arundell, Viscount, 1805-1876, 1849, undated (Box 26, Folder 976)
  - Ganz, Wilhelm, 1833-1914, 1905 (Box 26, Folder 977)
  - Gardiner, Robert William, Sir, 1781- 1864, 1826 (Box 26, Folder 978)
  - Gardiner, Samuel Rawson, 1829-1902, 1880-91, undated (Box 26, Folder 979)
  - Gaselee, Stephen, Sir, 1762-1839, undated (Box 26, Folder 980)
  - Gaselee, S. (Stephen), 1882-1943, 1905 (Box 26, Folder 981)
  - Gatty, Alfred Scott, Sir, 1847-1918
    Related Materials
    See Scott-Gatty, Alfred, 1847-1918, Box 54, folder 1946.
  - Gauntlett, Henry J. (Henry John), 1805-1876, 1879-93 (Box 26, Folder 982)
  - Geikie, Archibald, Sir, 1835-1924, 1896, undated (Box 26, Folder 983)
  - Geikie, Cunningham, 1824-1906, undated (Box 26, Folder 984)
  - George III, King of Great Britain, 1738-1820, 1780, undated (Box 26, Folder 985)
  - George V, King of Hanover, 1819-1878, 1833 (Box 26, Folder 986)
  - George William Frederick Charles, Duke of Cambridge, 1819-1904, 1863-91 (Box 26, Folder 987)
  - Gibbs, Thomas, 1839 (Box 26, Folder 988)
  - Gibson, Edgar C. S. (Edgar Charles Sumner), 1848-1924, 1894-1908 (Box 26, Folder 989)
  - Gibson, Thomas Milner, 1806-1884, 1851-75 (Box 26, Folder 990)
  - Giddens, George, 1855-1920, 1886-90, undated (Box 26, Folder 991)
  - Giffen, Robert, Sir, 1837-1910, 1893, undated (Box 26, Folder 992)
  - Gifford, Edric Frederick, Baron, 1849- 1911, 1886 (Box 26, Folder 993)
  - Gifford, George Markham, Sir, 1813- 1870, 1861 (Box 26, Folder 994)
  - Gilbert, Alfred, 1854-1934, 1887-97 (Box 26, Folder 995)
  - Gilbert, Ashurst Turner, 1786-1870, 1852-67 (Box 26, Folder 996)
  - Gilbert, Charles, 1866-1910, undated (Box 26, Folder 997)
  - Gilbert-Carter, Gilbert, Sir, 1848- 1927, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 998)
  - Gilchrist, Murray, 1868-1917, 1900-01 (Box 26, Folder 999)
  - Gill, C., undated (Box 26, Folder 1000)
  - Gillman, W., undated (Box 26, Folder 1001)
  - Gladstone, Catherine (Glynne), d. 1900, 1879, undated (Box 27, Folder 1002)
  - Gladstone, Helen, 1849-1925, 1897, undated (Box 27, Folder 1003)
  - Gladstone, Henry Neville Gladstone, Baron, 1852-1935, 1890 (Box 27, Folder 1004)
  - Gladstone, Herbert John Gladstone, Viscount, 1854-1930, 1881-1920 (Box 27, Folder 1005)
  - Gladstone, John, Sir, 1764-1851, 1825 (Box 27, Folder 1006)
  - Gladstone, J. H. (John Hall), 1827-1902, undated (Box 27, Folder 1007)
  - Gladstone, John Neilson, 1807-1863, 1847 (Box 27, Folder 1008)
  - Gladstone, Stephen Edward, 1844-1920, undated (Box 27, Folder 1009)
  - Gladstone, Thomas, Sir, Bart., 1804- 1889, 1836 (Box 27, Folder 1010)
  - Gladstone, W. E. (William Ewart), 1809- 1898, 1843-96, undated (Box 27, Folder 1011)
  - Gladstone, William Henry, 1840-1891, 1866, undated (Box 27, Folder 1012)
  - Gleichen, Edward, Lord, 1863-1937, 1881-97, undated (Box 27, Folder 1013)
  - Gleichen, Feodora Georgina Maud, Lady, 1861-1922, undated (Box 27, Folder 1014)
  - Gleichen, Valda, Countess, undated (Box 27, Folder 1015)
  - Glenesk, Algernon Borthwick, Baron, 1830-1908, 1874-84, undated (Box 27, Folder 1016)
  - Glenister, Thomas, 1881 (Box 27, Folder 1017)
  - Gloucester, Henry William Frederick Albert, Duke of, 1900-1974, 1828-35, undated (Box 27, Folder 1018)
  - Glover, Charles William, 1806-1863, 1851, undated (Box 27, Folder 1019)
  - Glover, J. H., 1857-58 (Box 27, Folder 1020)
  - Glover, Stephen, 1813-1870, 1862 (Box 27, Folder 1021)
  - Glover, William Howard, 1819-1875, 1861 (Box 27, Folder 1022)
  - Glyn, Edward Carr, Bp. of Peterborough, 1843-1928, 1913, undated (Box 27, Folder 1023)
  - Glyn, Isabella (Gearns) Dallas, 1823- 1889, 1886, undated (Box 27, Folder 1024)
  - Glynne, Stephen Richard, Sir, 1807- 1874, undated (Box 27, Folder 1025)
  - Goddard, Arabella, 1836-1922, 1869, undated (Box 27, Folder 1026)
  - Godfrey, Charles, 1839-1919, 1887 (Box 27, Folder 1027)
  - Godfrey, Dan. (Daniel), 1831-1903, 1893 (Box 27, Folder 1028)
  - Godson, Clement, 1845-1913, 1860-1910 (Box 27, Folder 1029)
  - Goff, Park, Sir, 1871-1939, undated (Box 27, Folder 1030)
  - Goldie, George Dashwood Taubman, Sir, 1846-1925, 1897-99 (Box 28, Folder 1031)
  - Goldie-Taubman, John Senhouse, Sir, 1838-1898, 1891 (Box 28, Folder 1032)
  - Goldingham, Mr., 1852 (Box 28, Folder 1033)
  - Goldney, Gabriel Prior, Sir, 1843-1925, 1894 (Box 28, Folder 1034)
  - Goldsmid, Julian, Sir, 1838-1896, 1895 (Box 28, Folder 1035)
  - Gomm, William Maynard, Sir, 1784-1875, 1865, undated (Box 28, Folder 1036)
  - Goode, William, 1801-1868, 1861-68 (Box 28, Folder 1037)
  - Goodeve, Florence Everilda (Knowlys), d. 1916, 1901 (Box 28, Folder 1038)
  - Goodford, Charles Old, 1812-1884, 1877 (Box 28, Folder 1039)
  - Goodwin, Harvey, 1818-1891, 1864-90, undated (Box 28, Folder 1040)
  - Gordon, Kitty (Mrs. W.W. Horsley- Beresford), 1897 (Box 28, Folder 1041)
  - Gordon-Cumming, William Gordon, Sir, Bart., 1848-1930, 1891 (Box 28, Folder 1042)
  - Gore, Mrs. (Catherine Grace Frances), 1799-1861, undated (Box 28, Folder 1043)
  - Gorst, John Eldon, Sir, 1835-1916, 1876-90 (Box 28, Folder 1044)
  - Goschen, George Joachim Goschen, Viscount, 1831-1907, 1895-1900, undated (Box 28, Folder 1045)
  - Gosford, Archibald Charles Montagu Brabazon, Earl of, 1877-1954, 1900 (Box 28, Folder 1046)
  - Gosse, Philip Henry, 1810-1888, 1868 (Box 28, Folder 1047)
  - Gough, Hugh Gough, Viscount, 1779-1869, 1866 (Box 28, Folder 1048)
  - Goulburn, Henry, 1784-1856, 1817-49 (Box 28, Folder 1049)